James F. McNulty Papers, 1925-2002
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 3: Legal / Business, 1929 - 2002
  - Series 1: Legal Case Files
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O.—B.A. Randall transaction, July 1952-December 1952 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O.—B.A. Randall transaction, January 1953-July 1953 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O.—B.A. Randall transaction, July 1954-September 1954 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., May 1931-August 1933 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., March 1934-September 1934 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., March 1935-December 1935 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., January 1936-March 1936 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., March 1940-September 1940 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., March 1943 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., August 1945-September 1946 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., September 1947-December 1947 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., January 1948-December 1949 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., May 1951-December 1951 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O., January 1952-July 1953 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—Maddern, Donald—Osborn partnership agreement, February 1964-June 1964 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files—Maddox, James A., June 1964-December 1964 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files—Maddox, James A., June 1964-December 1964 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Legal Files—Magoffin, John O., February 1953-October 1953 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Legal Files—Magoffin, John O., July 1952-August 1952 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Legal Files—Magoffin, John O., September 1952-December 1952 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Legal Files—Magoffin, John O., January 1955-December 1955 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Legal Files—Magoffin, John O., February 1956-November 1957 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Legal Files—Magoffin, John O., March 1958-July 1958 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Legal Files—Magoffin, John O., April 1950-January 1961 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Legal Files—Magoffin, John O.—Magoffin-Spurgeon-Graham partnership, February 1955-March 1955 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Legal Files—McCleave, Bonnie C., June 1978-March 1982 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Legal Files—McCormick, William C., August 1978-August 1979 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Legal Files—McCormick, William C., September 1979-September 1981 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Legal Files—McCulloch, Charles and Georgine, September 1979-November 1982 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Legal Files—McDevitt, Nadine, August 1977-February 1981 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files—McDaniel, Gertrude Rhea, January 1974-May 1981 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files—McDonough, Frank and Maria, January 1981-May 1981 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files—McIntyre, Macel—Real Estate, May 1973-August 1973 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—McIntyre, Macel—Real Estate, November 1978-January 1980 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files—McLeod, Nora B., December 1974-September 1980 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—McLeod, Nora B., January 1981-April 1952 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files—McPherson, M.E., September 1963-May 1964 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files—Rural Medical Programs, March 1974-May 1975 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Legal Files—Rural Medical Programs, October 1977-April 1978 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Legal Files—M and M Bank, Perrin, Arizona Livestock Exchange, December 1912-July 1938 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Legal Files— M and M Bank, Perrin, Arizona Livestock Exchange, January 1939-April 1939 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Legal Files— M and M Bank, Perrin, Arizona Livestock Exchange, May 1939-September 1939 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Legal Files—M and M Bank—Laney, November 1944-November 1953 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files—M and M Bank—Laney, June 1954-June 1955 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files—Prison Reform, October 1972-December 1972 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files—Prison Reform, January 1973-August 1973 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—Probate Committee, November 1975 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files—San Jose Lodge, November 1978-September 1985 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—S.B. 119, February 1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files—Second Division Cochise County Superior Court, January 1965-March 1965 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files—Second Division Cochise County Superior Court—pamphlets, fact book, 1970-1973 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Legal Files—Warren district recreation center, June 1955-December 1955 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Legal Files— Warren district recreation center, January 1956-November 1956 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Legal Files— Warren district recreation center, April 1958-August 1958 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Legal Files— Warren district recreation center, April 1959-May 1960 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Legal Files— Warren district recreation center—budgets, 1955-1959 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Series 2: Business Files
    - Business Files—Cochise Junior College, 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Business Files—Cochise Junior College—Administrative papers, 1964-1966 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Business Files—Cochise Junior College—Business Law, 1964-1966 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Business Files—Cochise Junior College—Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Business Files—Cochise Junior College—Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Business Files—Cochise Junior College—Pamphlets, 1964-1967 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Business Files—DSET—Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Business Files—DSET—Releases, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Business Files—DSET—Reports, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, April 1993-May 1993 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, June 1993-August 1993 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, September 1993-November 1993 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, December 1993 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, January 1994-February 1994 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, March 1994 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, April 1994-May 1994 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, June 1994-July 1994 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, August 1994-September 1994 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, October 1994 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, November 1994-December 1994 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, January 1995-February 1995 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, March 1995-May 1995 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, June 1995-July 1995 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, August 1995-September 1995 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, October 1995-November 1995 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, December 1995-January 1996 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, February 1996-March 1996 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, April 1996 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, May 1996-June 1996 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, July 1996-August 1996 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, September 1996-October 1996 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, November 1996-December 1996 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, January 1997 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, February 1997 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, March 1997-April 1997 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, May 1997 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, June 1997 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, July 1997-August 1997 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, September 1997-October 1997 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, November 1997-December 1997 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, January 1998-February 1998 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, March 1998-April 1998 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, May 1998-June 1998 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, July 1998- August 1998 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, September 1998-October 1998 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, November 1998-December 1998 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, January 1999-March 1999 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, April 1999-May 1999 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, June 1999-August 1999 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, September 1999-Novemeber 1999 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, December 1999-February 2000 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, March 2000-May 2000 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, June 2000-October 2000 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, November 2000-December 2000 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, January 2001-February 2001 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, March 2001-June 2001 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, July 2001-November 2001 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, December 2001-January 2002 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, February 2002-April 2002 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Legal – General – Correspondences, May 2002-November 2002 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Legal – General – Memorandum, January 1993-November 1996 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Legal – General – Memorandum, January 1997-December 1997 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Legal – General – Memorandum, February 1998-August 1999 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Subgroup 4: Personal / Family, 1935-1995
  "Personal/Family," contains personal and family materials collected between 1953-1986. Series One consists of personal correspondence that is arranged chronologically. There are also several files that are by topic that have been kept in their original order. Series Two contains items from his personal and family life such as items relating back to his high school days at Boston Latin and his time in the military.
  - Series 1: Personal Correspondence, 1953 – 1994
    - Personal Correspondence, 1930’s (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1955-April 1955 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, May 1955-December 1955 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1956-June 1956 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, July 1956-December 1956 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1957-September 1957 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Personal Correspondence, October 1957-December 1957 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1958-June 1958 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, July 1958-December 1958 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1959-June 1959 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, July 1959-December 1959 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1960-June 1960 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, July 1960-December 1960 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1961-May 1961 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1961-December 1961 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1962-May 1962 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1962-December 1962 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1963-May 1963 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1963-December 1963 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1964-April 1964 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, May 1964-October 1964 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, November 1964-December 1964 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1965-March 1965 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 1965-September 1965 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, October 1965-December 1965 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1966-February 1966 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, March 1966-May 1966 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1966-December 1966 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1967-August 1967 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, September 1967-December 1967 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1968-May 1968 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1968-December 1968 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1969-May 1969 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1969-December 1969 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1973-March (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 1973-May (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, May 1973-December 1973 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1974-August 1974 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, September 1974-December 1974 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1975-March 1975 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 1975-July 1975 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, August 1975-October 1975 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, November 1975-December 1975 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1976-March 1976 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 1976-June 1976 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, July 1976-October 1976 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, November 1976-December 1976 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1977-February 1977 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, March 1977 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 1977-May 1977 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1977-July 1977 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, August 1977 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, September 1977-October 1977 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, November 1977 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, December 1977 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1978-February 1978 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Personal Correspondence, March 1978 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 1978 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, May 1978 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1978-July 1978 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, August 1978-September 1978 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, October 1978 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, November 1978 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, December 1978 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1979 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, February 1979 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Personal Correspondence, March 1979 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 2, 1979-April 19, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 20, 1979-April 30, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Personal Correspondence, May 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1979 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, July 1979 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, August 1979 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, September 1979 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, October 1979-November 1979 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, December 1979 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence—pamphlets, 1980-1982 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1980-March 1980 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 1980-May 1980 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1980-July 1980 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, September 1980 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, October 1980 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, November 3-November 12, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, November 17-November 28, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, December 1980 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 5-January 13, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 14-January 28, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Personal Correspondence, February 3-February 13, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Personal Correspondence, February 16-February 27, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Personal Correspondence, March 1981 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 1981 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, May 1981 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 5-June 23, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 24-June 30, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, July 1981 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, August 1981 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, September 1981 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, October 1981 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, November 1981-December 1981 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, January 1982 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, February 1982 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, March 1982 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, April 1982 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, May 1982 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, June 1982-July 1982 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, August 1982-September 1982 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, October 1982-December 1982 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1980-1994 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Personal Correspondence, No Date (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Personal Correspondence—author, October 1966-December 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence—Cochise Fine Arts, inc., February 1975-July 1975 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence—House construction, April 1959-August 1962 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence—Junior College, 1958 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence—NIMLO (city), No Date (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence—Olympics, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence—Phoenix home, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence—Phoenix home, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence—Post office, 1965-April 1967 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Personal Correspondence—Post office, June 1967-October 1968 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Personal Correspondence—School, university, military, 1943-1947 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Personal Correspondence—Udall, Morris, April 1976-August 1977 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Personal Correspondence—Udall, Morris, September 1977-December 1984 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Personal Correspondence—Veterans Administration, 1952-1960 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Personal Correspondence – Kennedy, John F., December 1959-August 1960 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Personal Correspondence – Johnson, Lyndon B., June 1960 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Personal Correspondence – Humphrey, Herbert, October 1959 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Series 2: Personal, 1935-1994
    - Personal—Arizona Alpha, No Date (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Personal—Boston Public Latin School, 1946 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Personal—Boston Public Latin School—Class reunion, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Personal—Boston Public Latin School—school letter, No Date (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Personal—Calendar, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Personal—Calendar, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Personal—Catechism of Christian Doctrine, Nancy McNulty, 1935 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Personal—Delta Sigma Rho, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Personal—Ireland Report, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Personal—McKale, James F., Memorial Service, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Personal—McNulty, Michael, No Date (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Personal—Miscellaneous, No Date (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Personal—Patches, World War II, No Date (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Personal—Programs—Rotary Club, 1973/1981 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Personal—Publication, 1960/1975 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Personal—Speeches, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Personal—Transcripts, No Date (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Personal—University of Arizona, No Date (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Personal—University of Arizona Law School—brief, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Personal—Editorial opinion pieces, 1987-1995 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Personal—Birthday part guest book, October 18, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Personal—University of Arizona College of Law Outstanding Graduate Award, May 12, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Personal—Thought pieces (includes background, quotes), No Date (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Personal—Bisbee Daily Review, 1935 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Personal—Political Cartoons, No Date (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Personal—Certificates of Achievement, 1959-1991 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Personal—Brewery Gulch Gazette: Death of J. F. K., November 28, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Personal—Ephemera, No Date (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Subgroup 5: Photographs
  "Photographs," contains photographs collected over the years and is divided into three series. Series One consists of photographs taken during McNulty’s 1962 visit to the USSR. The series contains both official and unofficial photographs as well as postcards collected during the visit. Series Two contains photographs taken during his time in the House of Representatives. This section includes photographs taken during the campaign. The series contains many photographs taken with prominent members of the House of Representatives as well as with many world dignitaries. Series Three, “Miscellaneous Photographs,” is arranged alphabetically according to subject. This section contains photographs taken while McNulty was in the military, at the University of Arizona, and through out his state political career. There are also photographs of McNulty with Robert Frost and with John F. Kennedy Jr.
  - Series 1: Delegation to the USSR, August 1962
    - Photographs—Delegation to the USSR, August 1962 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Photographs—Delegation to the USSR—official photographs, August 1962 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Photographs—Delegation to the USSR—postcards, August 1962 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Photographs—Delegation to the USSR—unofficial photographs, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Series 2: U.S. House of Representatives
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives, No Date (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives, No Date (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives, No Date (Box 87, Folder 7)